[Music]
hello my name is Dr Gil um I've been
asked to do perform a general
examination on yourself before we start
could you please confirm your name and
date of birth yeah my name is Megan
sters and my date of birth is the 22nd
of February 1998 super thank
you so in terms of doing the examination
today that's going to involve having
look at your hand
having a look at um your face getting
you to um do some maneuv for me we're
also going to have a look at your chest
we're going to do your Vital Signs and
we'll also have a look at your legs is
that okay Y super so to start off if I
can see your hands
please okay so I can't see anything on
toward there if you could turn your
hands over
please okay no obvious issues to P our
hands out straight and we're checking
for a a initial Tremor and then we also
want to the wrist back so we're
going to go on I'm just going to take
your pulse on both
sides okay then checking the pulse
super say you've got a normal pulse
there and also a normal respiratory
raise I'm just going to check your
arm okay and there's a normal pulse
there as well so I'm just going to have
a look at your eyes if I might so if you
could look up for
me okay and then look down for
me super can you show me your teeth okay
and show me your tongue
okay and put your tongue to the roof of
your mouth please super that's fine so
I'm now just going to do your blood
pressure do you have any problems with
either of your arms no
super so we're going to do this twice
we're going to do it once with the
stethoscope and then once with so just
checking the
size okay that's fine over the
artery and then coming
around okay and just relax for me
so the pulse has
disappeared and the pulse returns at
about
98 okay so we're just going to do that
again with the
stethoscope okay can relax the arm fold
just putting that over the artery
okay we're going a little bit
higher and I can hear the sounds that
get at
100 and they've disappeared at 68 so
normal blood pressure there thank
you so just going to check uh your
temperature at this point
okay we got a normal temperature all in
the green and we're just going to check
uh the oxygen saturations at this point
we just have a finger for me thank
you okay so we've got 99% stat that's
absolutely
fantastic okay you swing your legs
forward and set
uh that way I'm now going to put my
hands on your neck if that's okay and
we're going to see if we can find any
lumps and bumps yep so if you can move
your hair backwards
please okay starting off under the
chin
okay and then front
behind okay and if you could shrug your
shoulders up for me please thank you and
relax down that's all fine so if you
could lie back again on the bed for me
so just having a look at uh your chest I
can't see any obvious issues in terms of
the skeletal appearance so you're going
to go down to your legs I'm going to
check for uh any problems with uh uh
edema down here any swelling so pressing
on both
sides and there's nothing there and then
the pulse is
behind there good and we've got normal
pulses there
so I couldn't find any abnormalities on
that General examination do you have any
questions for myself no super thank you
very much for your time
[Music]